vmoptions.in 2013-12-08

# Privacy - VMO Classifieds, Free Indian Classified Ads, Local India Classifieds

**Privacy Policy** ****

A privacy policy states how you will respect the privacy of your website users.It says what information you will gather, how you will use it and how you will keep it secure.

A privacy policy is a legal document that discloses some or all of the ways a party gathers, uses, discloses and manages a customer's data. The exact contents of a privacy policy will depend upon the applicable law and may need to address the requirements of multiple countries or jurisdictions. While there is no universal guidance for the content of specific privacy policies, a number of organizations provide example forms.

**Collection**

Information posted on Vmoptions.in is obviously publicly available. Therefore, if you choose to provide us with personal information, you are consenting to the transfer & storage of that information on our servers. We collect & store the following personal information:

1\. Email address, physical contact information, & (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information; 

2\. Computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to & from vmoptions.in & ad data (all through cookies – you can take steps to disable the cookies on your browser although this is likely to affect your ability to use the site); 

3\. Other information, including users ip address & st&ard web log information.

**Use. We use users' personal information to:**

1\. Provide our services; 

2\. Resolve disputes, collect fees, & troubleshoot problems;

3\. Encourage safe trading & enforce our policies; 

4\. Customize users' experience, measure interest in our services, & inform users about services & updates ;

5\. Communicate marketing & promotional offers to you; 

6\. Do other things for users as described when we collect the information. 

**Disclosure**

1\. All information contained by Vmoptions.in is treated as strictly confidential & Vmoptions.in does not & will not disclose or share such confidential information to / with any external organization. 

2\. The users' privacy is very important to us. We do not & shall not at any point in time, either sell or rent users' personal information to third parties without users' explicit consent. 

3\. We may be required from time to time to disclose users' personal information to Governmental or law enforcing agencies or our regulators, but we will only do so under proper authority.

4\. Vmoptions.in also reserves the right to make use of the personal information in any investigation or judicial process relating to fraud on account of such transactions during the period Vmoptions.in retains such information. 

5\. We may also disclose personal information to enforce our policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other's rights, or protects anyone's rights, property or safety.

6\. We may also share personal information with:

7\. Corporate affiliates who help detect or prevent potentially illegal acts & provide joint services (Our corporate affiliates will market only to users who ask them to).

8\. Service providers who help with our business operations.

**Using Information from Vmoptions.in**

You may use personal information gathered from Vmoptions.in only to follow up with another user about a specific posting, not to send spam/ phising or collect personal information from someone who hasn't agreed to that.

**Access, Modification, & Deletion**

You can see, modify or erase your personal information by reviewing your posting or account status page. Contact us to review any personal information we store that is not available on Vmoptions.in. There may be a charge associated with such requests but these will not exceed the amounts permitted by law. We delete personal information when we no longer need it for the purposes we described earlier. We retain personal information as permitted by law to resolve disputes, enforce our policies; & prevent bad guys from coming back.

**Data Security**

We use a number of mechanisms (encryption, passwords, physical security) to protect the security & integrity of your personal information against unauthorized access & disclosure. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. So while we strive to protect such information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us & you do so at your own risk. Once any personal information comes into our possession, we will take reasonable steps to protect that information from misuse & loss & from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.

**Confidentiality of Information**

Users who use any of the features on Vmoptions.in agree & accept that they have been fully informed by Vmoptions.in that the use of features may lead to publication, to all users of Vmoptions.in, of any personal information posted by them while using any specific feature on Vmoptions.in. Users further agree that the authenticity of, & consequences from the posting by users of any personal information of themselves or any other person, are the sole responsibility of the user. Users further agree & accept that the terms of the Privacy Policy will be applicable to the use of all features, existing & new. However, the Users agree & accept that confidentiality of information posted on such features has been waived by the Users of such features themselves.

**General**

We may update, upgrade, modify (partially &/or fully) this policy at any time, Send questions about this policy to our Support Team . [  
](mailto:info@sntinfotech.com)
